<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BioC Asia 2021</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BioC Asia 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 18:52:14 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 18:52:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>test test</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of conduct</title>
      <link>/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code/</guid>
      <description>This code of conduct is developed for the virtual Bioc Asia 2021 conference. For more details, see the Bioconductor Code of Conduct
Social media policy Images and content from talks, workshops, and posters may be shared publicly through social media (Twitter, etc.). Videos will be released on the Youtube Bioconductor channel. Please, inform the organizing committee as soon as possible if you don&amp;rsquo;t wish your presentation material to be shared. The Bioconductor conference aims to provide a supportive, collegial, and harassment-free environment Bioconductor is dedicated to providing a supportive, collegial, and harassment-free conference experience for everyone, regardless of:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Members of organizing committees Bold highlights leaders of the committees</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributed talks</title>
      <link>/contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contributions/</guid>
      <description>THE FOLLOWING TIMES ARE ALL JAPAN TIME
day1 (15:00~) Omar El-Ashkar: &amp;ldquo;rGenomeTracks: Extending epigenetic visualization methods in R&amp;rdquo; High throughput sequencing technologies have been proved useful in a plethora of omics. Epigenomics is an area of active research that innovatively blends different biological techniques with sequencing to gain new insight into epigenetic regulations like chromatin accessibility, genome topology and nucleosome positioning. One of the cornerstones of analyzing such data is to be able to visualize it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>link to recruiting platform &#39;tayo&#39;</title>
      <link>/jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jobs/</guid>
      <description>Here is a link to the recruiting platform called &amp;ldquo;tayo&amp;rdquo; for Japanese graduate students and researchers. Since &amp;ldquo;tayo&amp;rdquo; is currently focused on Japan, we will only introduce it in Japanese.
本ページでは大学院生や研究者に向けた、求人プラットフォーム tayo へのリンクを掲載します。
tayo.jp 研究分野の求人情報にご興味をお持ちの方はぜひ御覧ください。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizers</title>
      <link>/organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/organizers/</guid>
      <description>Organizing committee                                Jianqiang Sun   Koki Tsuyuzaki   Kozo Nishida   Mahmoud Ahmed   Marcel Ramos                  Matt Ritchie   Peter Hickey   Satoshi Kume   Tom Kelly   Xueyi Dong    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Past Conferences</title>
      <link>/conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/conferences/</guid>
      <description> Bioconductor 2021 EuroBioC 2020 BioC Asia 2020 Bioconductor 2020 Bioconductor 2019 Bioconductor 2018 Bioconductor 2017 Bioconductor 2016 Bioconductor 2015 Bioconductor 2014 Bioconductor 2013 Bioconductor 2012 Bioconductor 2011 Bioconductor 2010 Bioconductor 2009 Bioconductor 2008 Bioconductor 2007 Bioconductor 2006 Bioconductor 2005  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration to the virtual Bioc Asia 2021 conference Registration link Fees Free</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Schedule All invited talk abstracts All contributed talk abstracts All workshop abstracts Click or change the place name in the left of &amp;ldquo;Powered by team up&amp;rdquo; (in the lower-right corner) to set your time zone.
You can also switch the calendar view from weekly view to agenda view. You can switch between them with the button on the left of the hamburger menu at the top right of the calendar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule</title>
      <link>/schedule_iframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/schedule_iframe/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submissions</title>
      <link>/submissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/submissions/</guid>
      <description>Abstract submission Access the BioC Asia 2021 abstract submission GitHub issue form
You must be logged in to GitHub to see the abstract submission GitHub issue form.
Please click the form link while logged in to GitHub.
Important dates  September 7, 2021: Registration opens September 8, 2021: Call for abstracts opens   September 30, 2021: Call for abstracts closes October 3, 2021: Notification of decision October 3, 2021: Second call for workshops opens October 8, 2021: Second notification of decision November 1-4, 2021: BioC Asia 2021  Submission types Birds-of-a-feather session 25 min talk, Free-format, organizer-lead interactive discussion session on a topic relevant to the Bioconductor community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshops/</guid>
      <description>The workshop will be held from 4pm to 5pm Japan time (UTC+09:00) from November 1st to 4th.
Japanese Workshops (Day1) 山本 博之 Hiroyuki Yamamoto: &amp;ldquo;Rを用いたメタボロームデータ解析: Metabolome data analysis using R&amp;rdquo; BioconductorパッケージXCMSを用いた、メタボロミクスにおける質量分析データ処理の手順を簡単に紹介する。次に、Rパッケージloadingsを用いた多変量解析の手順を紹介する。loadingsパッケージは、メタボロームデータを可視化するだけでなく、主成分負荷量やPartial last squares 負荷量とそれらの統計的仮説検定を用いて、有意な代謝物を選択することが出来る。
I will briefly introduce the procedure for mass spectrometry data processing in metabolomics using the R Bioconductor package “XCMS”. And, I will also introduce the procedure for multivariate analysis using R package “loadings”. The “loadings” package can not only visualize metabolome data, but also select significant metabolites using Principal component loadings, Partial least squares loadings and their statistical hypothesis testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>行为准则</title>
      <link>/code-mandarin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code-mandarin/</guid>
      <description>该行为准则为Bioc Asia 2021虚拟会议而制定。 欲知更多详情，请参阅 Bioconductor行为准则 。
社交媒体政策 演讲、研讨会和海报中的图像和内容可以通过社交媒体（如Twitter等）共享。 视频将会在 Youtube Bioconductor 频道上发布。如果您不希望您的演讲材料被共享，请尽快告知组委会。 Bioconductor 会议致力于提供支持、融洽且无骚扰的环境 Bioconductor 会议致力于为每个人提供支持、融洽且无骚扰的环境， 无论：
 性别、性别认同和表达、性取向、残疾、外貌、体型、种族、年龄、宗教信仰等。 知识立场：数据分析方式、软件偏好、代码风格、科学观点等。  此虚拟活动行为准则适用于BiocAsia2021虚拟活动和交流，包括但不限于虚拟平台、演讲、研讨会、海报会议、社交活动、slack、线上及社交媒体交流。我们不能容忍对参会者的骚扰、恐吓或欺凌。色情文字和图像不宜出现于演讲、交流与在线场所，包括聊天。
违反这些规则的参会者可能会由会议组织者酌情处罚或开除出会。我们的反骚扰政策详见 https://bioc2020.bioconductor.org/code_of_conduct 。
不可接受的骚扰、恐吓和欺凌行为的示例 骚扰包括但不限于：
 在聊天中向公众或个人发表贬低或侮辱他人的评论 在线分享色情图片 骚扰摄影或录音 持续扰乱讨论或其他活动 不受欢迎的性关注 提倡或鼓励上述任何行为  恐吓和欺凌包括但不限于:
 在公开演讲中针对某人的攻击性或威胁行为 嘲笑或侮辱他人的智力、工作、观点或问题/评论 在科学讨论中提及某人的性别、性别认同和表达、性取向、残疾、外貌、体型、种族、年龄、宗教信仰或其他个人属性 故意排挤某人  执行 与会者当被要求停止骚扰行为时应立即遵守。
如果与会者有骚扰行为，活动组织者保留采取任何行动以确保为所有与会者提供友好环境的权利。这包括警告违规者或将其开除出会。
活动组织者可能会采取行动纠正任何旨在扰乱活动或使环境对任何与会者不利，或在相关方面具有明显影响的行为。
我们希望与会者在所有会场和与活动相关的在线活动中都能遵守这些规则。
报告 如果有人让您或其他任何人感到不安全或不受欢迎，请尽快报告。 骚扰和其他违反行为准则的行为会降低此活动对每个人的价值。 我们希望您愉悦地参与我们的活动。正是像您这样的人，让我们的活动变得更美好。
您可以选择个人或匿名举报。
匿名或非匿名举报 您可以通过此链接进行匿名或非匿名举报： https://tinyurl.com/bioccomplaint 。这是一个自由格式的文本框，会被转发给行为准则委员会。
我们无法直接向您跟进匿名举报，但我们会对其进行全面调查并采取一切必要措施防止其再次发生。
个人举报 您可以直接向任意一位会议反骚扰委员会成员进行个人举报：Kozo Nishida。
在进行个人举报时，我们将确保您是安全的且不会被偷听。其他活动工作人员可能会参与其中以确保妥善管理您的报告。在安全的情况下，我们将请您告诉我们发生了什么。这可能会让您感到不安，但我们会尽可能以尊重的方式处理，您也可以找人陪同并支持您。您不会被要求与任何人对质，我们也不会告诉任何人您是谁。
行为准则违规举报  电子邮件： code-of-conduct@bioconductor.org 匿名行为准则违规举报： https://tinyurl.com/bioccomplaint  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>行動規範</title>
      <link>/code-japanese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code-japanese/</guid>
      <description>この行動規範は、Bioc Asia 2021 バーチャルカンファレンス用に策定されています。さらに詳しい点については、Bioconductorの行動規範を参照してください。
ソーシャルメディアポリシー トーク、ワークショップ、ポスターの画像やコンテンツは、ソーシャルメディア (Twitterなど) を通じて公開される可能性があります。 ビデオは Youtube の Bioconductor チャンネルで公開される予定です。 発表資料の共有を希望されない場合は、できる限り早く組織委員会(organizing committee)にご連絡ください。
Bioconductor のカンファレンスは、協力的で、合議的で、ハラスメントのない環境を提供することを目指しています Bioconductor は、以下にかかわらず、すべての人に協力的で、合議的で、ハラスメントのないカンファレンス体験を提供することに専念しています:
 性別、性同一性や表現、性的指向、障害、容貌、体の大きさ、人種、年齢、または宗教。 学問的立場: データ分析へのアプローチ、ソフトウェアの好み、コーディングスタイル、科学的視点、など。  バーチャルイベントの行動規範は、BiocAsia2021 のバーチャルイベントおよびコミュニケーションに適用されます。 これには、バーチャルのプラットフォーム、トーク、ワークショップ、ポスターセッション、ソーシャルアクティビティ、slack、オンラインおよびソーシャルメディアコミュニケーションが含まれますが、これらに限定されません。 カンファレンス参加者へのハラスメント、脅迫、いじめは容認しません。 性的な言葉や画像は、プレゼンテーション、コミュニケーション、オンライン会場(チャットを含む)でふさわしくありません。
これらのルールに違反するカンファレンス参加者は、カンファレンス主催者の裁量により、制裁を受けるか、会議から追放される場合があります。 私たちのハラスメント防止ポリシーは https://bioc2020.bioconductor.org/code_of_conduct で見ることができます。
容認できないハラスメント、脅迫、いじめ行為の例 ハラスメントには以下が含まれますが、これらに限定されません:
 聴衆に、または個人的に、他の人を軽蔑したり侮辱するコメントをチャットで行う 性的な画像をオンラインで共有する 嫌がらせの写真や録音 トークやその他のイベントのしつこい妨害 歓迎されない性的な注目のされ方 上記の行動のいずれかを擁護またはけしかけること  脅迫やいじめには以下が含まれますが、これらに限定されません:
 公開プレゼンテーション中に誰かに向けられた攻撃的または脅す行動 他人の知性、仕事、視点、または質問/コメントを嘲笑または侮辱すること 科学的議論の文脈で、誰かの性別、性同一性と表現、性的指向、障害、容貌、体の大きさ、人種、年齢、宗教、またはその他の個人的属性に言及すること 故意に誰かを歓迎されていないと感じさせること  執行 ハラスメント行為の停止を求められた参加者は、直ちに従うことが求められます。
参加者がハラスメント行為を行った場合、イベント主催者は、イベントをすべての参加者にとって快適な環境に保つために、あらゆる措置を執る権利を有します。これには、違反者への警告や会議からの退出処分も含まれます。
イベント主催者は、イベントを混乱させたり、参加者にとって状況を非友好的にするように計画された、あるいは明らかな影響を与える行為を是正するための措置を執ることができます。
私たちは、参加者がすべてのイベント会場およびイベント関連のオンライン活動でこれらの規則に従うことを求めます。
報告 誰かがあなたや他の誰かに不安なもしくは嫌な思いをさせた場合は、できるだけ早く報告してください。 ハラスメントやその他の行動規範違反は、すべての人にとって私たちのイベントの価値を下げるものです。 私たちは、あなたが私たちのイベントで幸せになることを望んでいます。あなたのような人が私たちのイベントをより良い場所にします。
報告は、個人的に、または匿名で行うことができます。
匿名・非匿名での報告 匿名・非匿名での報告はこちらからお願いします: https://tinyurl.com/bioccomplaint。
これは自由記述のテキストボックスで、会議の主催者に転送されます。
匿名の報告を直接追跡調査することはできませんが、十分に調査し、再発防止のために必要な措置を講じます。
個人的な報告 カンファレンスのハラスメント防止委員会のいずれか（例: 西田孝三）に個人的な報告をすることができます。
個人的な報告を受ける場合、スタッフはあなたの安全を確保し、その情報が漏洩しないようにします。 ただし、あなたの報告が適切に管理されるように他のイベントスタッフが関わる場合はありえます。 安全が確保されたら、何が起こったのかを話していただきます。 動揺されるかもしれませんが、できる限り丁重に対応します。 サポートしてくれる人に同伴していただくことも可能です。 誰かと対面するように求められることはありませんし、あなたが誰であるかを誰かに伝えることもありません。</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
